A Guide to the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (CCCA) records FA484
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (CCCA) Meetings, 1
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller's CCCA materials, 1.3
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of Individuals and Communities in the USA, Notebook of Background Materials, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life: Trends, Problems, Objectives and Decisions, Hudson Institute, Draft, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of Individuals and Communities in the USA, Daniel P. Moynihan Report, 1975 June (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Correspondence and Memorandum on CCCA, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 203)
    - Correspondence, Notes and Panel Meeting Materials, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - Introductions and Outlines of Panels, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 205)
    - Introduction and Reports of Panel 1-V Meetings, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 206)
    - Significant National Trends and Policies, Derived from material prepared by the NYS Division of the Budget, 1974 July (Box 24, Folder 207)
    - Significant National Trends and Policies, Derived from material prepared by the NYS Division of the Budget, 1974 July (Box 24, Folder 208)
    - Technology Development and the National Purpose, Hans Mark, 1974 August (Box 24, Folder 209)
- Administrative, 2
  - Contracts, 2.1
    - Consultants A-01 (1) - (13), 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 210)
    - Consuitants A-01 (14) - C-01(8), 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 211)
    - Consuitants A-01 (14) - C-01(8), 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 211.1)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Restricted from scholarly access.
    - Consultants C-02 (1) - C-05.1(13), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 112A)
    - Consultants C-02 (1) - C-05.1(13), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 112A.1)
    - Consultants C-05.2 (1)- C-05.2 (17), 1974 (Box 25, Folder 113A)
    - Consultants C-05.3 (1)- C-05.4 (12), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 114A)
    - Consultants C-05.3 (1)- C-05.4 (12), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 114A.1)
    - Consultants C-05.6 (1)- C-05.7 (15), 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 115A)
    - Consultants C-05.6 (1)- C-05.7 (15), 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 115A.1)
    - Consultants C-05.8 (1)- D-07 (3), 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 116A)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 117A)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 117A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 118A)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 118A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Expenses, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 119A)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 120A)
    - Geographic Studies: Africa, C-05.7, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 120A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Asia, C-05.4, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 121A)
    - Geographic Studies: Asia, C-05.4, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 121A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Asia, C-05.4, Expenses, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 122A)
    - Geographic Studies: Asia, C-05.4, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 123A)
    - Geographic Studies: Asia, C-05.4, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 123A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Latin America, C-05.6, CSIS, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 124A)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Contracts, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 125A)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Contracts, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 125A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Contracts, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 126A)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 127A)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 127A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 128A)
    - Geographic Studies: Middle East, C-05.2, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 128A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 129A)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 129A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 130A)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 130A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 131A)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 131A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 132A)
    - Geographic Studies: Soviet Union, C-05.3, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 132A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 133A)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 133A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 134A)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 134A.1)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Expenses, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 135A)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 136A)
    - Geographic Studies: Western Europe, C-05.1, Miscellaneous and General, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 136A.1)
    - Kristol, Irving, A-01, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 137A)
    - Kristol, Irving, A-01, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 138A)
    - Kristal Study, Daniel Moynihan, A-01(16), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 139A)
    - List of General, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 140A)
    - Payments, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 141A)
    - Payments, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 141A.1)
    - Payments Under Contracts, A-01- C-05.2, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 142A)
    - Payments Under Contracts, C-05.3- D-07, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 143A)
    - Panel I, Contracts, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 144A)
    - Panel II, Completed Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 145A)
    - Panel III, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 146A)
    - Panel IV, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 147A)
    - Panel VI, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 148A)
    - Berger, Stephen, A-05 (2), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 149A)
    - Bing, George, C-05.8 (1), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 150A)
    - Bing, George, C-05.8 (1), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 150A.1)
    - Bruce-Briggs, Barry, A-05 (3), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 151A)
    - Campbell, Rodney, D-07 (3), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 152A)
    - Campbell, Rodney, D-07 (3), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 152A.1)
    - Cone, Sydney M. III, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 153A)
    - Conservation Foundation, A-05 (9), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 154A)
    - Cook, Gary M., A-05 (4), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 155A)
    - CSIS: The Center for Strategic and International Studies, Dr. Abshire, A-04 (1), 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 156A)
    - Deutch, Michael J., A-03 (1), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 157A)
    - Dunlop, John T., A-05 (7), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 158A)
    - Kaufman, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 159A)
    - Kaufman, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 159A.1)
    - Lambright, W. Henry, A-05 (5), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 160A)
    - Lloyd Free Institute for International Social Research, A-02 (1), 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 161A)
    - Logue, Ed, A-05 (13), 1975 (Box 30, Folder 162A)
    - Mark, Hans, A-05 (8), 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 163A)
    - Mitre Corporation, C-06 (11), 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 164A)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., A-01(16), 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 165A)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., A-01(16), 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 165A.1)
    - Research Planning Association, Steinberg, C-01 (2), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 166A)
    - Rocliff Associates, D-07 (2), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 167A)
    - Rostow, Walt W. and Elspeth Rostow, A-05 (6), 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 168A)
    - Sansom, Robert, Energy and Environmental Analysis, C-01 (1), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 169A)
    - Shultz, George P., 1974 (Box 30, Folder 170A)
    - Smith, Bruce, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 171A)
    - Smith, Bruce, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 171A.1)
    - Stanford Research Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 172A)
    - SUNY at Binghamton Research Foundation, McHale, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 173A)
    - Teller, Edward, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 174A)
    - Teller, Edward, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 174A.1)
    - Truman, Edwin M., 1974 (Box 30, Folder 175A)
    - Weaver, Pat, D-07 (1), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 176A)
    - Weaver, Pat, D-07 (1), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 176A.1)
  - Corporate Matters, 2.2
    - Agreements, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 177A)
    - Automobiles, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 178A)
    - Budget, Actual thru 1974 April 30, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 179A)
    - Budget, Actual thru 1974 June 30, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 180A)
    - Budget, Actual thru 1974 September 30, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 181A)
    - Budget, Actual thru 1974 December 31, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 182A)
    - Budget, Actual thru 1975, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 183A)
    - Budget, Proposed, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 184A)
    - Building Maintenance Et Al Contracts, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 185A)
    - By-Laws of the Third Century Corporation, 1973 August 14 (Box 31, Folder 186A)
    - Charitable Organization Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 187A)
    - Chart of Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 188A)
    - Charter of the Third Century Corporation, 1973, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 189A)
    - Contracts no Longer in Force, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 190A)
    - Credit Cards, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 191A)
    - Electricity Arrears 20 W. 55 Street, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 192A)
    - Federal Funding, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 193A)
    - Furniture, Fixtures and Equipment Owned and Rented, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 194A)
    - Geographic Studies, Revised Budgets, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 195A)
    - House judiciary Committee Correspondence, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 196A)
    - Minutes of the First and Second Meetings of the CCCA, 1973 December 4 and 1974 April 1 (Box 32, Folder 197A)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting, 1973-1976 December 4 (Box 32, Folder 198A)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting, 1975 June 20 (Box 32, Folder 199A)
    - Minutes of the Board of Directors, the Executive Committee, and the Investment Committee, 1973 August-1976 January (Box 32, Folder 200A)
    - Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 June 13, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 201A)
    - NAR, Agreement to Use 55th Street, 1973-1976 (Box 32, Folder 202A)
    - NAR, Agreement to Use 55th Street, Greenwald, C. File, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 203A)
    - NAR, Announcement of Creation of Commission, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 204A)
    - NAR, Guarantee Agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 205A)
    - NAR, Guarantee Agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 206A)
    - NAR and LSR, Initial Gift of Securities, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 207A)
    - NAR, Resignation, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 208A)
    - New York State Study of the Role of the Modern State in a Changing World, undated (Box 33, Folder 209A)
    - New York State Study of the Role of the Modern State in a Changing World, undated (Box 33, Folder 210A)
    - Prospectus of the Corporation, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 211A)
    - Public Support Calculations, 1973-1975 (Box 33, Folder 212)
    - Records sent to 5600, Books and Files, 1976 November 9 (Box 33, Folder 213)
    - Records sent to 5600, 1976 November 11, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 214)
    - Requests for Gifts, 1967, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 215)
    - Resignation of Officers and Members, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 216)
    - Workpapers, Budget etc., 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 217)
    - Workpapers, Budget etc., 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Fundraising, 2.3
    - Alternative Sources, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 219)
    - Dwayne Andreas Foundation, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 220)
    - Vincent Astor Foundation, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 221)
    - Vincent Astor Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 222)
    - Vincent Astor Foundation Annual Report, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 223)
    - Vincent Astor Foundation Annual Report, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 224)
    - Brown Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 225)
    - Business Roundtable, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 226)
    - Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 227)
    - Congressional Fundraising, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 228)
    - Contributions and Gifts, 1973-1976 (Box 34, Folder 229)
    - Contributions Received, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 230)
    - Contributions Received, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 231)
    - Fairchild Foundation, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 232)
    - Foundation Luncheon Group, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 233)
    - Foundation - Mellon, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 234)
    - Fund Solicitation Mailing, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 235)
    - Greenwall, Mr. and Mrs. Frank K, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 236)
    - Marron, Don, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 237)
    - National Science Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 238)
    - National Science Foundation, Energy Study Plan Proposal, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 239)
    - National Science Foundation, Energy Study Plan Proposal, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 239.1)
    - National Science Foundation, Notes and Materials, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 240)
    - National Science Foundation, Notes and Materials, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 240.1)
    - National Science Foundation, Notes and Materials, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 241)
    - Paley, William S. Charitable Trusts, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 242)
    - Piszek, Edward J., 1974 (Box 35, Folder 243)
    - Readers Digest, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 244)
    - Teller, Edward, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 245)
    - The Sulzberger Foundation, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 246)
    - Thomas J. Watson Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 247)
    - Whitney, John Hay, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 248)
    - Registrations, General, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 249)
    - Registrations, General, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 250)
    - Registrations, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 251)
    - Registrations, Arkansas, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 252)
    - Registrations, California, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 253)
    - Registrations, Colorado, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 254)
    - Registrations, Connecticut, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 255)
    - Registrations, Georgia, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 256)
    - Registrations, Hawaii, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 257)
    - Registrations, Illinois, 1974-1979 (Box 37, Folder 258)
    - Registrations, Iowa, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 259)
    - Registrations, Kansas, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 260)
    - Registrations, Maryland, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 261)
    - Registrations, Massachusetts, 1974-1977 (Box 37, Folder 262)
    - Registrations, Michigan, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 263)
    - Registrations, Minnesota, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 264)
    - Registrations, Nebraska, undated (Box 37, Folder 265)
    - Registrations, New Jersey, 1974-1978 (Box 37, Folder 266)
    - Registrations, New York, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 267)
    - Registrations, North Carolina, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 268)
    - Registrations, North Dakota, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 269)
    - Registrations, Ohio, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 270)
    - Registrations, Oklahoma, undated (Box 37, Folder 271)
    - Registrations, Oregon, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 272)
    - Registrations, Pennsylvania, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 273)
    - Registrations, South Carolina, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 274)
    - Registrations, Washington State, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 275)
    - Registrations, Wisconsin, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 276)
  - Publication records, 2.4
    - Author Signoff, Quality of Life, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 277)
    - Author Signoff, Quality of Life, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 278)
    - Authors Signoff, Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 279)
    - Authors Signoff, Trade, Inflation and Ethics, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 280)
    - Author Signoff, Values of Growth, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 281)
    - Budget, Publishing, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 282)
    - Budget, Publishing, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 283)
    - Copyright Certificate, 1981, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 284)
    - Distribution of Volumes, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 285)
    - Geographic Studies, Editorial Change Approval, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 286)
    - Heath, Contract Background, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 287)
    - Heath, Final Contract, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 288)
    - Heath, Payments, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 289)
    - Letters to the Authors Announcing Plans to Publish Studies, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 290)
    - Letters to Authors whose studies were NOT Published, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 291)
    - Letter to Commission Members and Contributors, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 292)
    - Libel Memorandum, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 293)
    - Non-profit Sale of Volumes, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 294)
    - Not Published, Adrian, Huber, Panel VI, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 295)
    - Not Published, Hughes, Wilson, Lapp, Panel I, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 296)
    - Not Published, Laffer, Ketchum, Panel IV, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 297)
    - Not Published, Lambright, Teich, Bezold, Panel VII, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 298)
    - Not Published, Manoff, Panel VI, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 299)
    - Not Published, Mitre Corporation, Transportation Study, Panel VI, undated (Box 39, Folder 300)
    - Not Published, Sansom, Robert, Energy and Environmental Analysis, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 301)
    - Not Published, Yokelson, Panel VI, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 302)
    - Release Announcing Publication of Series, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 303)
    - Requests to Commission for rights to publish studies elsewhere, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 304)
    - Rights to Publish Commission Studies (re language of consultants contracts), 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 305)
    - Royalties, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 306)
    - Permissions, Foster and Colvin, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 307)
    - Permissions, Gardner, David, Panel IV, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 308)
    - Permissions, Geographic Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 309)
    - Permissions, Kristol Study, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 310)
    - Permissions, Panel I Study, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 311)
    - Permissions, Panel II Study, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 312)
    - Permissions, Panel IV Study, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 313)
    - Permissions, Special, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 314)
    - Permissions, Vital Resources, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 315)
    - Permissions and Releases, Conservation Foundation, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 316)
    - Permissions and Releases, Kristol Study, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 317)
    - Permissions and Releases, Panel I, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 318)
    - Permissions and Releases, Panel II, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 319)
    - Permissions and Releases, Panel IV, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 320)
    - Permissions and Releases, Panel IV, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 321)
    - Permissions and Releases, Special, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 322)
    - Press Releases, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 323)
- Financial and Personnel records, 3
  Conditions Governing Access
  Personnel records, and select financial records, are restricted from scholarly access.
  - Financial records, 3.1
    Select financial records are restricted from scholarly as access, as noted.
    - Arthur Young and Company, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 324)
    - Cash Book and Ledger, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 325)
    - Cash Book and Ledger, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 326)
    - Closing Entries, 1975 December 31, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 327)
    - Functional Coding Cashbook, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 328)
    - Functional Codes I and II, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 329)
    - IRS Letter of Determination and Exemption Certificate, 1973-1977 (Box 42, Folder 330)
    - Tax Exemption Certificates, State and Local, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 331)
    - Tax File, General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 332)
    - Tax Forms, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 333)
    - Tax Return for 1973, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 334)
    - Tax Returns for 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 335)
    - Tax Returns for 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 336)
    - 1973, Financial Statement, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 337)
    - 1974, Financial Statement, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 338)
    - 1975 Financial Statement (Box 43, Folder 339)
    - 1976 Financial Statement, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 340)
    - 1977 Financial Statement (Box 43, Folder 341)
    - 1973 Cash Receipts and Disbursements (Box 44, Folder 342)
    - 1974 Cash Disbursements (Box 44, Folder 343)
    - 1974 Cash Receipts (Box 44, Folder 344)
    - 1975 Cash Disbursements (Box 44, Folder 345)
    - 1975 Cash Receipts (Box 44, Folder 346)
    - 1976 Master (Illegible) (Box 44, Folder 347)
    - 1976 Payroll Register (Box 44, Folder 348)
    - 1973 Ledger (Box 45, Folder 349)
    - 1974 Second Quarter (Box 45, Folder 350)
    - 1974 Third Quarter (Box 45, Folder 351)
    - 1974 Fourth Quarter (Box 45, Folder 352)
    - 1975 First Quarter (Box 45, Folder 353)
    - 1975 Second Quarter (Box 45, Folder 354)
    - 1975 Third Quarter (Box 45, Folder 355)
    - 1975 Fourth Quarter (Box 45, Folder 356)
- Correspondence, 4
  - Albert, Carl, 1973 September-November (Box 50, Folder 462)
  - Allen, Ivan, 1973 July-1974 March (Box 50, Folder 463)
  - Anderson, Martin, 1973 October-1974 August (Box 50, Folder 464)
  - Anderson, Robert O., 1973 August-1974 July (Box 50, Folder 465)
  - Armstrong, Anne, 1974 February-April (Box 50, Folder 466)
  - Astor, Brooke, and Forty Under Forty Materials, 1974 January-May (Box 50, Folder 467)
  - Baker, William, 1973 August-1974 July (Box 50, Folder 468)
  - Berger, Stephen, 1973 August-1974 January (Box 50, Folder 469)
  - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1973 August-1974 July (Box 50, Folder 470)
  - Borlaug, Norman Ernest, 1973 November-1974 September (Box 50, Folder 471)
  - Boyer, Ernest, 1973 December-1974 April (Box 50, Folder 472)
  - Braun, Ted, 1974 February-August (Box 50, Folder 473)
  - Calabresi, Guido, 1973 October-1974 July (Box 50, Folder 474)
  - Diamond, Henry, 1973 December-1974 October (Box 50, Folder 475)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1973 November-1974 August (Box 50, Folder 476)
  - Form Letters, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 477)
  - Forrester, Jay W., 1973 (Box 50, Folder 478)
  - Foster, John S. Jr., 1973 September-1975 June (Box 50, Folder 479)
  - Foster, Luther, 1973 September-1974 July (Box 50, Folder 480)
  - Free, Lloyd, 1973 June-1975 April (Box 51, Folder 481)
  - Hanks, Nancy, 1973 November-1974 July (Box 51, Folder 482)
  - Johnson, Belton Kleberg, 1973 November-1974 July (Box 51, Folder 483)
  - Jones, Clarence B., 1973 November-1974 May (Box 51, Folder 484)
  - Kahn, Herman, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 485)
  - Kirkland, Joseph Lane, 1973 August-1974 June (Box 51, Folder 486)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1973 December-1974 March (Box 51, Folder 487)
  - Knowles, John P., 1973 November-1974 August (Box 51, Folder 488)
  - Kresky, Mary, 1973 May and September (Box 51, Folder 489)
  - Landes, David, 1973 December-1974 October (Box 51, Folder 490)
  - Lawrence, Mary Wells, 1973 September-1974 October (Box 51, Folder 491)
  - Levy, Walter, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 492)
  - Linowitz, Sol, 1973 November-1975 June (Box 51, Folder 493)
  - Logue, Edward, 1973 December-1974 August (Box 51, Folder 494)
  - Lubell, Sam, 1973 September (Box 51, Folder 495)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1973 October-1974 November (Box 51, Folder 496)
  - Maginnes, Nancy, 1974 February (Box 51, Folder 497)
  - Malik, Charles, 1973 December-1974 September (Box 51, Folder 498)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1973 October-1975 February (Box 51, Folder 499)
  - Mark, Hans, 1973 August-1974 March (Box 52, Folder 500)
  - Mark, Hans, 1974 April-October (Box 52, Folder 501)
  - McCracken, Paul, 1973 November-1974 August (Box 52, Folder 502)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1973 August-1974 July (Box 52, Folder 503)
  - Myerson, Bess, 1973 August-1974 August (Box 52, Folder 504)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller (NAR) Thank you Letters, 1974 April (Box 52, Folder 505)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1973 February-May (Box 52, Folder 506)